

# **SUMMARY**

Experienced Junior Web Designer.
I have worked full web development process in a team, and working as UI Developer remotely to improve my skill.

I love hiking, and discovering new places, but above all, I enjoy thinking of userexperience when making websites. Also, I am so into studying code!

### **PROFICIENCY**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- WordPress
- GitHub
- JavaScript
- BootStrap

## **CONTACT**

- kateyeeum.com
- hello@kateyeeum.com
- github.com/yiyeum
- codepen.io/KateYeeum
- twitter.com/KateYeeum
- facebook.com/yiyeum

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

KANTUKAN (Front-End Developer)
 November 2016 ~ Current

Working as developer freeter at system development depart of Kantukan company. My main role is developing UI page based on mockup created by designers. I also really enjoy communicating on Slack to understand the mission and work with team members!

ARTIST PORTFOLIO

November 2016 ~ Current Final Project from BCIT | WordPress | Team project

Wordpress artist portfolio website made for Canadian Artist Aimee Henny Brown with skilled team members. We built information architecture, wireframe, HD mockup based on discovery meeting with a client. My main role in development was creating Press and Resource pages. It was an amazing team project for one month and a half with daily meetings!

### **EDUCATION**

 British Columbia Institute of Technology Computer Systems | January 2017 ~ Current

Studying software development languages including Java, C, and C++. Also learning discrete mathematics and computing concept. I do love learning code!

- British Columbia Institute of Technology
   Technical Web Designer | May 2016 ~ November 2016

   Intensive six-month program to learn major languages
   which used in web design field. Also, we had a chance
   to work for a real client for the final project. This program
   was my turning point getting into the computing field!
  - British Columbia Institute of Technology
     Business Essentials | September 2015 ~ Current

Learned essential business skills including Marketing, Public-speaking, Accounting, Business Math and Business English writing. I have good fundamentals of Business!